From comic to screen, discover the making of Marvel's first heroes.
Marvel Studios Assembled: The Making of Eternals is a
documentary film directed by Bradley Hogan.
Join director Chloe Zhao and the Cast of Eternals as they recount their experiences
during the making of Marvel Studios’ most ambitious film to date.
Discover how the ensemble cast felt stepping into their roles, filming in remote locations, and creating
bonds that would help to create the on-screen relationships that span over 7,000 years.
Self - Sersi, played by Gemma Chan.
Self - Producer, played by Nate Moore.
Self - Dane Whitman, played by Kit Harington.
Self - Kingo, played by Kumail Nanjiani.
Self - Makkari, played by Lauren Ridloff.
Self - Producer, played by Kevin Feige.
Marvel Studios: Assembled is an American anthology television docuseries
of specials created for the streaming service Disney+.
Produced by Marvel Studios, each special goes behind-the-scenes of a Marvel Studios Disney+ series or film, particularly those
within the Marvel Cinematic Universe (MCU), with the creatives, exploring the process of creating each series or film.
The series was first announced in February 2021.
Marvel Studios: Assembled premiered on March 12, 2021, with subsequent specials releasing
shortly after a Disney+ series' completion or a film's Disney+ release.
14 specials were released for Phase Four of the MCU, followed by 9 specials released for Phase Five projects through
2024, including one for the first season of the Marvel Studios Animation series X-Men '97 (2024).
The special for Agatha All Along (2024) was released for free
on Marvel Entertainment's YouTube channel.
Assembled received positive responses for showcasing how each series or film came
together, particularly with the technical aspects and franchise connectivity.